(いの)うわぁ～!!
な 何なの これ？ 敵の術？
Wh-What is this?!
The enemy's Jutsu?!
(ヒナタ)な なめくじ!?
A-A slug...?!
(サクラ)綱手様の口寄せ
カツユ様よ。
It's Katsuyu-sama,
summoned by Tsunade-sama.
ごめんなさい。
すみません。
- I'm sorry.
- Forgive me.
Why are you here?
どうして こちらに？
(シズネ)
きてくださったのですね カツユ様。
You came to help us, Katsuyu-sama?
(カツユ)綱手様は
前回渡した封印術式だけでは➡
Tsunade-sama has
been concerned about
尾獣相手に
どれほどの効果があるのかと➡
the Sealing Jutsu's effectiveness
against the Tailed Beast.
心配されておいででした。
それで 私に 封印術のための
チャクラを 皆様に運ぶようにと。
She sent me to bring you
the Chakra for the Sealing Jutsu.
助かります。
That will be a big help.
さっそく 皆様に
分け与えましょう。
Let me distribute it to you.
お願いします。
かしこまりました。
Please proceed.
Very well...
(鱗児)綱手め
カツユを送り込んできたか クソッ。
That Tsunade!
She sent Katsuyu...
Crap... More!
もっとだ！ もっと力を
幽鬼丸！
More power! Yuukimaru!
(幽鬼丸)うわぁ～!!
(紅蓮)ナルト。
Naruto!
(ナルト)何だってばよ！
What is it?
許されるのか？
Will I be forgiven...?
いや 許してくれるのか？
I mean! Will he forgive me?
母親を殺したのが
私だと知ったら➡
When Yuukimaru finds out that
I'm the one who killed his mother?
幽鬼丸は…。
Sheesh! Are you still
mulling over that?
はぁ… まだ そんなこと
迷ってんのかよ。
幽鬼丸を この手で守る覚悟なら
できている。
I'm prepared to protect Yuukimaru.
オレだったら思い続ける。
If I were you, I'd keep thinking of him!
嫌われようが 拒まれようが➡
Even if I'm despised,
or rejected, or hated!
たとえ 憎まれようが。
アイツが オレのことを 帰る場所だって
思おうが思わなかろうが➡
Whether he... thinks that I'm
the place to return to or not
そんなことは関係ねえ。
has nothing to do with it!
I'd keep on thinking about him.
オレなら思い続ける。
あっ！
そうだな。 私も ナルト➡
Yeah, you're right!
I'll become the fool too...
just like you, Naruto.
お前みたいに バカになってみる。
なんだと!?
What?!
急ぐぜ。
Let's hurry!
《幽鬼丸》
Yuukimaru!
水面下からの三尾の力が…。
I feel the power of the Three-Tails
beneath the water's surface...
すごい 今にもチャクラが爆発しそう。
I-It's enormous... I feel like
the Chakra will explode any minute.
こ こんな…。
Th-This much?
Without Katsuyu-sama's Chakra,
my power alone couldn't...
カツユ様のチャクラがなきゃ
私の力だけじゃ とても…。
いい 三尾の力が
大蛇丸のものになろうが➡
Listen! If the Three-Tails falls into
the hands of Orochimaru
or the Akatsuki...
暁の手に落ちようが➡
木ノ葉にとって
すさまじい脅威になる。
It will be disastrous
for the Hidden Leaf...
でも 今 三尾は
我々の手の中にある。
But the Three-Tails is
in our hands right now...
木ノ葉の里を 仲間たちを
この力から守れるのは➡
The only ones who can protect
our comrades in Hidden Leaf Village
私たちだけよ。
(３人)はい！
from this power is us!!
- Right!
カツユ様 チャクラを
更に 強めていただけませんか？
Katsuyu-sama... Can you increase
your Chakra even further?
はい やってみます。
Yes... I will try.
一気に 異空間封印にまで
持っていきます！
We will take it to the other dimension
all at once.
う～ん！
R-Right.
クッ ヤツらめ まだ
三尾を抑えこんでいるのか。
Th-They're still trying to
control the Three-Tails.
うわ～！
幽鬼丸！
三尾の荒ぶる魂を刺激しろ！
Yuukimaru, arouse the spirit
of the Three-Tails! Make it go wild!
暴れろ 木ノ葉のヤツらを
すべて蹂躙してしまえ！
Trample the Hidden Leaf!
うわ～！
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Memory of Guilt
(キバ)サイ お前もヤツらに？
Sai, did they attack you too?
Yeah...
(サイ)ええ 幽鬼丸を
連れ去られてしまいました。
They got Yuukimaru!
(赤丸)ワンワン！
(テンテン)これは…。
This is...?
(リー)間違いありません
ヤツらです！
No doubt about it! It's them!
待ちなさいよ！
わあ！
Wait!
Wh-What are you doing?!
It's time to get revenge!
何をするんです
ど根性で リベンジしましょう！
今 飛び込んでも
同士討ちする危険性があるでしょ。
If we jump in now, there's a chance
we'll hit each other with friendly fire.
ああ あの霧のなかでは
赤丸の鼻も利かねえ。
Yeah, even Akamaru's sense of smell
will be useless.
クーン。
ここは しばらく
様子をみましょう。
We must wait and see.
Oh man! This is so frustrating!
んもう！ 悔しいです！
《カカシ : 敵は 幽鬼丸を使い➡
It seems the enemy is using
Yuukimaru to control the Three-Tails.
三尾を
コントロールしようとしているのか》
《このままでは
シズネの封印班が危ない》
At this rate, Shizune's Sealing team
is in danger.
《ちょっと厄介だな。
It's a touchy situation...
この数の分身
すべてをかわすのは 不可能》
Countering all these clones
is impossible!
It's no good!
ダメだ よけきれない!!
I can't dodge them all!!
うわ～！
(鬼霧)そろそろだ 煙縛牢！
It's about time...
Binding Smoke Prison!
ハハハッ 噂に聞く 木ノ葉のカカシよ。
To think that I would have the chance
to personally bring down
オレのこの手で倒せるチャンスに
めぐりあえるとは…。
the fabled Kakashi
of the Hidden Leaf.
It's worth surviving...
人生 生き延びてみるもんだぜ。
Wha--?!
オレも お前ほどじゃないが
影分身が使えるんだよ。
Although not to your extent, I use
Shadow Clones too.
雷切！
Lightning Blade!
《ヤマト : まずいな》
This is bad.
(鬼鳳)何とかと煙は
高いところが好きってね。
They say, something and smoke
like high places.
煙龍！
Smoke Dragon!
The Wood Style is useless
against smoke,
自在に形を変える煙に木遁は不利。
which changes form on its own.
ならば こちらも
スタイルを合わせるまで。
Then, I must adapt my style...
水遁！ 水波手！
Water Style! Hand of Waves!
なに？
What?
気体である煙は
水で液化してしまえば➡
Smoke is a vapor and by
liquefying it with water...
自在にコントロールできない。
it can't be controlled freely.
Not against me and my Water Style.
水遁を扱えるボクには
もうお前の術は無意味だ。
Your Jutsu is meaningless now.
あっ あ～っ！
(濡羅吏)受けなさい！
Take this!
第三の手があることを忘れないで。
Don't forget that I have a third arm.
遊びは終わり。
Playtime is over.
ムダよ。
It's useless!
(シノ)放錘の陣。
Spindle Formation!
うわっ！ なぜ なぜなの？
Why... Why?!
お前の術は オレの蟲たちに
とっては かなりの強敵だった。
Your Jutsu was quite formidable
against my insects.
しかし 日向一族のヒナタと
一戦交じえたのが お前の敗因だ。
However... the cause of your defeat
lies in the fact that you fought with
Hinata of the Hyuga Clan.
To explain...
なぜ なら…。
((シノ : ヒナタ 話しがある。
Hinata, I need to speak with you.
シノ君 どうしたの？
Shino, what's wrong?
あの晶遁使いについて
些細なことでもいい➡
Any little thing will do.
Can you tell me anything about
that Crystal Style user?
何か気づいたことがあれば
教えてほしい。
残念だけど 彼女の術は完璧。
Unfortunately, her Jutsu is flawless.
とっさに全身をチャクラで
覆っていなければ 今頃私は…。
Had I not covered my entire body with
Chakra just in time... By now, I'd be...
全身にチャクラといえば シノ君。
Speaking of Chakra covering
the entire body...!
Shino, watch out for that slimy guy!
あのヌルっとした人には気をつけて。
シノ君に とっては 強敵になる。
He will be a formidable opponent
against you.
どういうことだ？
Why is that?
His Jutsu is his entire body.
敵の術は 体そのもの。
あのボディスーツの中は
チャクラで満たされていて➡
That body suit is filled with Chakra
and he's able to
change his form at will.
体型を自在に
変化させることができる。
柔拳を打ち込んだときも➡
I used my Gentle Fist against him
and he just twisted his body away.
体をねじまげ
すり抜けるようにかわされたの。
柔拳をかわしただと。
He countered your Gentle Fist...
問題は そのときかすめた
私の手についた液体のほう。
The problem was the body fluid that
got onto my hand when I grazed it.
敵の体は 全身そのとりもちの
ような 粘液に覆われてる。
The enemy's entire body is covered
with mucous that looks like birdlime.
(ん？))
事前に情報は得ていた。
I had prior data, so from the start...
だから はじめは
そのやっかいな粘液を➡
I concentrated on scraping that
troublesome mucous off your body.
お前の体から
そぎ落とすことに集中した。
お前 はじめから！
Since we started...?!
Yes! I focused my attacks on making
that mucous membrane
そう。 お前のその粘液の膜を
少しでも薄くするために。
さらに攻撃を
一点に集中させたことで➡
as thin as possible so that it would
break easily.
薄い膜は簡単に破けた。
終わりだ。
ギャーッ!!
That is all.
終わったか？
ええ。
It's over...?
時間はかかったが。
Yes...
It took some time but...
(キバ)カカシ先生！
(赤丸)ワンワン！
Kakashi-sensei!
(リー)ご無事でしたか。
You're all okay...
キミたちこそ 大丈夫かい？
What about you guys?
まぁ なんとか。
Well... we made it somehow.
But what about Naruto?
それより ナルトは？
まだ見つからない。
We haven't found him yet.
(サイ)すみません 幽鬼丸を。
ああ。
I'm sorry about Yuukimaru...
さて 我々は
封印班の側面援助に向かうぞ。
Now then, we'll head out
to assist the Sealing team.
(みんな)はい！
- Yes!
- Right!
それと もうひとつ。
幽鬼丸を奪還保護すること。
And also, we will recover
and protect Yuukimaru!
まずは封印班の様子を 見に行く。
But first, we'll see how
the Sealing team is doing.
どうやら苦戦中のようだしな。
They seem to be in a difficult battle...
今度こそ… 三尾を！
This time, for sure...
This time... the Three-Tails...
いの 焦らないで。
Ino... you don't need to rush it.
チャクラを安定させることに
精神を集中させるのよ！
Just focus your mind on
stabilizing your Chakra.
は はい！
Y-Yes...
ぐおぉ～!!
ダメか!? まだ足りないのか!?
No good... It's not enough.
うぅ… うっ うぅ…！
この!! ダメなのか!?
Damn it! It's not working!
幽鬼丸の力はそんなものなのか!?
Is that all there is
to Yuukimaru's power?!
こんなもんじゃ もう効かない。
This isn't gonna work anymore.
フッ！
こうなったら最後の手段だ。
Then I've got to use the last measure,
although I didn't want to resort to it...
これだけは使いたくなかったがな。
大蛇丸様のために
死んでもらうよ！
You're gonna die
for Orochimaru-sama's sake.
あっ あぁ… あっ！
さあ!!
Here!
うっ…！
幽鬼丸！
大丈夫か!?
Yuukimaru!
お前たち！
やっぱり生きていたか！
Are you all right?
So you guys were alive after all...
しっかりしろ！
どうした!?
Snap out of it! What happened?
あぁ… あっ あぁ…。
おい！ 幽鬼丸！
しっかりしてくれ！
Hey Yuukimaru! Wake up!
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
フンッ。
やっぱり…
帰ってきてくれたんだね。
You came back... after all... Guren-san;
because I was thinking of you...
紅蓮さん… ボクが思っていたから。
思っている人がいるところが
帰ってくる場所 だから。
Wherever someone is thinking of you,
that's the place to return to...
ああ… そうさ。
Yes... that's right.
お前が思っていてくれたから
帰ってこられたんだ。
You were thinking of me,
that's why I was able to come back.
うん…。
三尾の異空間の中に
閉じ込められていた間➡
Uh-huh...
When I was trapped in
that other dimension
inside the Three-Tails,
all I thought about was you...
ずっと 私も
お前のことを思っていた。
だから 幽鬼丸は 私のところへ
帰ってこなくちゃいけないんだ。
That's why you have to
return to me too, Yuukimaru...
嬉しいな… ボクは帰るよ。
紅蓮さんのところへ。
I'm so happy.
I'm coming back to you, Guren-san...
ボクの帰るところは
紅蓮さんのところしかないんだ。
You're the only one I can return to.
フフッ… ハハハッ…。
ああ そうさ。
Yeah right.
That's the only place left for you...
お前の帰るところは
もう そこだけしかないんだ。
帰るべき母親の懐は
なくなってしまったからな。
Since you can't go running back
to your mama's bosom anymore.
やめろ。 お前は黙ってろ。
Stop! Just shut up.
いや これだけは言わせてもらう。
No, let me just say this...
聞くんだ 幽鬼丸！
Listen! Yuukimaru!
黙れって言ってるんだ。
I said to shut up!
いいんだ ナルト…。
It's all right, Naruto...
だけどよ…。
いいんだ… お前が
教えてくれたから…。
But...
It's all right! You taught me...
紅蓮…。
Guren...
フッ… ハッハッハッハッ！ 覚悟の上か。
So you're prepared...?
立派なもんだ。 いいか？ 幽鬼丸。
How noble. Listen, Yuukimaru!
お前の帰るべき場所を
奪ったのは➡
The one who stole the place
you should return to...
白い椿を お前の母親の血で
赤い椿にしたのは…。
The one who turned
the white camellia
red with your mother's red blood...
お前の母親を殺したのは
その女…。
The one who killed your mother
is that woman...
紅蓮なんだ!!
Guren!
紅蓮の本性は 悪魔なのさ。
母親を殺したことを隠し➡
Guren is actually an evil demon!
She hid the fact that
she killed your mother,
お前を利用するために
近づき 信用させ➡
and got close to you to win your trust;
just to use you.
利用し続けてきたんだからな！
And she has continued to use you!
ハハ… ハハハハハ！
幽鬼丸！ 憎いだろう？
殺してやりたいだろう？
Yuukimaru! Don't you hate her?!
Don't you want to kill her?
誰も止めやしない。 止めるもんか。
No one will stop you...
As if I'd stop you!
さあ その怒りを三尾にぶつけろ!!
Now take your anger out
on the Three-Tail!
三尾に何もかも すべて
壊してしまえと命じるんだ ハハ…。
And order the Three-Tails
to destroy everything!
この野郎が!!
Why you...!
黙れ！
Shut up!
フッ… ハハハハハ。
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
すまない 幽鬼丸…
アイツの言ったことは本当だ…。
I'm sorry... Yuukimaru.
What he says is true.
聞くんだ 幽鬼丸。
昔の紅蓮は 大蛇丸のために➡
Please listen to me, Yuukimaru.
The Guren of the past committed
many terrible sins
たくさんの罪を
犯したかもしんねえ。
in order to serve Orochimaru.
But Guren is different now!
でも 今の紅蓮は違う！
今までのことを
悔やんで 悔やんで 悔やんで…。
She regrets all the things in her past.
She's filled with regret!
何があっても
幽鬼丸 お前を守るって…。
And no matter what happens,
she will protect you!
どんなに嫌われても お前のことを
思い続けるって オレに誓ったんだ。
No matter how much
you may hate her,
she will keep on thinking about you.
She swore that to me.
どんなに悔いても 謝っても
私の犯した罪が➡
I fully realize that no matter
how much I may regret it,
no matter how many times
I say I'm sorry
決して消えることはないのは
わかっている。
nothing will ever erase what I did.
お前が望むなら
この命を奪ってもかまわない。
If you wish me dead, kill me.
I won't care.
でも もし許されるなら➡
But... but if you can forgive me...
お前のことを
ずっと守り続けていたい。
I will protect you forever.
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
あっ…。
そんな…
私のことを憎まないのか？
You're not going to hate me?
紅蓮さんは いい人だよ。
You're a nice person Guren-san...
やっぱり 紅蓮さんのいるところが
ボクの帰るべき場所だもん。
You are the one
I should return to, after all...
紅蓮さんも ボクのいるところに
帰ってくればいいんだよ。
And I'm the one
you should return to, Guren-san.
誓う。 もう お前のそばから
離れることはない。
I promise you...
I will never leave your side.
I will always think of you.
お前のことをずっと思い続ける。
うん。
Uh-huh... And I will
always think of you, Guren-san.
ボクは ずっと紅蓮さんのことを
思い続けているよ。
これからも ず～っと。
For now, and forever...
ず～っと 大好きだよ。
And ever... I love you.
ああ 私もだ。
Yeah, me too.
お前たち
もう絶対 離れるんじゃねえぞ。
The two of you...
Never be parted again!
フフフフ… とんだ茶番だよ。
What a farce... You weaklings
can lick each other's wounds...
弱い者同士が
傷をなめあったって➡
そんな絆なんて
すぐに ちぎれるものだ。
But a bond like that will break easily!
フッ…。
ふっ！
What...?!
カブト… テメエ！
Kabuto! You...!
(カブト)ナルト君。
Naruto-kun...
ジャマするなら キミも殺すよ。
If you get in the way,
I'll kill you too.
カブト！ テメエが全部やったのか!?
Kabuto! You're behind all of this?!
許さねえ!!
You won't get away with it!
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
Kabuto, just what are
you guys aiming to do?!
It's not only the Hidden Leaf
and the Akatsuki...
but all the Hidden Villages will soon
engage in long, fierce clashes.
What?!
Orochimaru-sama has his eyes
on that violent future...
That was the plan, but...
Why you--! That's all gibberish to me.
Guren! Go with Yuukimaru!
Protect him no matter what!
I won't let you do that.
You two will not be freed.
Shattered Promise
Next time: "Shattered Promise"
なぁなぁなぁ！ シノの素顔って➡
Hey you guys.
誰も見たことねえよな。
そういえば…。
No one has ever seen
Shino's real face, right?
Now that you mention it...
でも キバなら
見たことあるんじゃない？
But haven't you seen his face, Kiba?
オレだって 見たことねえよ。
Nope, I've never seen it either.
つうか あんま興味ねえし。
ヒナタは どうだ？
Not that I care.
What about you, Hinata?
わ… 私も見たことない。
I-I've never seen him.
う～ん 誰も見たことねえとなると
ますます気になる！
Hmm... If no one has seen his face,
I'm even more curious.
(サクラ)意外に
サスケ君みたいにクールかも！ フフーッ！
Maybe he's pretty cool, like Sasuke.
(キバ)サスケの どこがいんだよ。
カカシ先生みたいじゃねぇの？
What's so great about Sasuke?
Maybe he's like Kakashi-sensei.
(サクラ)ずいぶんマヌケ面ね。
確かに！
Then he looks pretty stupid.
That's for sure...
(ヒナタ)リーさんみたいな目は
どうかな？
H-How about eyes like Lee?
はっ ゲジマユ？ わっ あっ 濃ゆ！
Huh? Bushy Brow?
S-So thick...
あっ だったらさ ギャップを狙って
お色気系とか？
Then how about something different,
a sexy type?
(シノ)オッホン！
(ナルトたち)あっ げっ！ シノ!?
Ahem...
Huh?! Shino!
- Shino...
しかたない。
お前らが そんなに言うなら…。
It can't be helped... If you all insist...
- What're you doing here?!
No, stop!